(Wil:)I wasn't.
(Penny:)Me, either.
(Leonard:)So, what do you think, is there a
professional downside to doing it?
(Wil:)Well, it's tricky.
(Wil:)You want to take projects
that you're excited about,
(Wil:)but sometimes you also
have to pay the bills.
(Wil:)When you're on the set
working on something
(Wil:)that you just know in your heart
is bad, not Star Trek...
Yeah, beam me up. I love it!
(Wil:)Anyway, those jobs
can be soul-crushing.
(Penny:)That's what I'm afraid of.
Well, I was in Stand By Ma
when I was a kid,
(Wil:)and it was a huge success.
(Wil:)The terrible movies I did
came after that.
(Wil:)Imagine how that feels.
(Leonard:)Sounds rough.
(Wil:)I'm telling you,
this business is brutal.
(Wil:)To this day,
I hate going on auditions.
(Wil:)Okay, I walk in, and I can just
feel them thinking,
"He was such a cute kid.
What happened to him?"